<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Industry Topics II - Blogs - Roberto Filho</title>
    <link>https://betosaud.000webhostapp.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Industry Topics II - Blogs - Roberto Filho</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 11:12:56 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://betosaud.000webhostapp.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile First</title>
      <link>https://betosaud.000webhostapp.com/post/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 11:12:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://betosaud.000webhostapp.com/post/post2/</guid>
      <description>What is it anyway? Mobile first is a concept, a break in patterns, vices, and paradigms that have been acquired over the years. It&amp;rsquo;s a strategy and a different way of looking at content that really matters on a website. Mobile devices are becoming more sophisticated and present in our lives. Even so, they often do not receive due importance during the process of creating and developing our sites. It was in this search for optimization that the mobile first was born: the focus on the user experience in mobile devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should designers know how to code?</title>
      <link>https://betosaud.000webhostapp.com/post/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 11:12:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://betosaud.000webhostapp.com/post/post1/</guid>
      <description>My perspective As a well rounded IT professional, I thought it was a good time to try a career change. I always was attracted by the design of things. I always liked to poke around with Photoshop and to be creative. Then I started to study web development and design. A whole new world opened up to me, in a bad way: All I could see before my eyes was everything I don&amp;rsquo;t know yet&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>